Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records Concerning Community Relations
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Secretary's office, Yale University, records concerning community relations
1939-1988
RU 53
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
44.75
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, reports, financial records, and related materials documenting Yale University's relations with the New Haven community, primarily from the late 1960s through 1988.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-D (YRG 4-D), Records documenting community relations of Yale University.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of the Secretary, 1977-1990.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, reports, financial records, and related materials documenting Yale University's relations with the New Haven community, primarily from the late 1960s through 1988.
Community and college; Universities and colleges -- Administration; University towns; New Haven (Conn.); Yale Council on Community Affairs; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Public relations; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Records concerning community affairs, 1966-1976; Accession 1977-A-006
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Correspondence
    - Interoffice, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Outgoing (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1970 May-Jul (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1970 Aug-Nov (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1970 Dec-1971 Feb (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1971 Mar-Apr (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1971 May-Aug (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 1971 Sep-Dec (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1972 Jan-Apr (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 1972 May-Sep (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1972 Oct-1973 Sep (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - 1973 Oct-1976 Apr (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Subject Files
    - Activities report, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Affirmative Action Compliance Program non-construction - Yale, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Affirmative Action plan, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Black arts, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Black Coalition (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 21 - 23)
      - Black Coalition Council, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Rockefeller project, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Student employment, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Black educators of New Haven, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Black workshop, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 30 - 31)
    - Citizens' Commission to Develop Quality Education, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System and New Haven public schools proposal, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Committee and Volunteer programs, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Community Housing, Incorporated, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Community involvement, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 36 - 38)
    - Community Progress, Incorporated, 1966-1971 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Compensatory education meeting, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Compensatory educational programs, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 41 - 42)
    - Compensatory educational synopses, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Connecticut Mental Health Center, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Crow, The: newspaper and journalism training program, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Dixwell Legal Rights Association, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Draft Board: letters, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Dwight Hall (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Economic Development, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Economic Development Proposal, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Education/Cultural Committee, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - English/Spanish Program, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Greater New Haven Business and Professional Men's Association, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Guest register, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Heritage Hall Development Corporation, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Hill Area Work Study Project, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Hill Arts Cooperative Film Program, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Hill Health Center, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Hill Housing Development Corporation, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Hill Neighborhood Corporation, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Hill Parents Association, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - History, activities, recommendations, 1967-1975 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Housing, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Housing Authority suit, 1968-1975 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Jambo Communications, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Junta for Progressive Action, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Lee High School Annex, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Life Enrichment Activity Program, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Lincoln Bassett students, field trips for: Dean Morgen, 1968-1973 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Manpower Consortium, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - May Day Weekend, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Mental Health Center, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Minutes, 1968-1973 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Minutes and current proposals, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Music program, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Narcotics Addiction Research and Community, Community Opportunities, Inc., 1968-1972 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Neighborhood nursery, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - New Colleges, Information on, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Object: Professions and Leadership (O.P.A.L.), 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - "Open Classroom" programs, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Operation Breakthrough Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Center, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Peabody Museum, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - People Organized in Neighborhood Trust, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Proposals, current, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Proposals, miscellaneous, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Public schools, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Puerto Rican Human Resources Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Recreation, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Regional Community Colleges Board of Trustees, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Reorganization (Box 8, Folder 97)
      - 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 98)
      - Luellen's material on, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 99)
      - Luellents material on, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 100)
      - Final draft of, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Residential Youth Center, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Rockefeller proposal, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Secretarial Training Program, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - State Senate and House of Representatives, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Station wagons, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Student employment report, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Student employment report, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Summer intern file, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Summer report, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Theater in the Streets, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Transitional Year Program, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Urban Employment Corps, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Vestibule training program (Box 9, Folder 115)
      - Policy procedure statement, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 116)
      - Roster, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 117)
      - Summer "68", 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Volunteer programs, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - Volunteer services, Herb Cahoon, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - W.Y.B.C., 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Yale-New Haven History Education Project, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Yale-New Haven Hospital, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - Financial Material
    - Administrative expenditures
      - 1971 (Box 11, Folder 124)
      - 1972 (Box 11, Folder 125 - 126)
      - 1973 (Box 11, Folder 127 - 128)
      - 1974 (Box 11, Folder 129 - 130)
      - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 131 - 132)
      - 1976 (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Background material on gift account, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 134)
    - Books, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 135)
    - Budget (Box 12, Folder 137)
      - 1972-1976 (Box 12, Folder 138)
      - Operating, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 139)
      - New, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 140)
      - Transfers, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 141)
    - Community projects, 1969-1976 (Box 12, Folder 142 - 145)
    - Computer Print-out Ledgers (Box 12, Folder 146)
      - Black Coalition, 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 147)
      - Cornunity advocate, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 148)
      - Contingency, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 149)
      - General appropriation, 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 150)
      - IBM gifts, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 151)
      - Office of Executive Director, 1968-1971 (Box 13, Folder 153)
      - Rockefeller: overstuffing manpower grant, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 154)
      - Statement of accounts (Box 13, Folder 155)
      - Student employment, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 156)
      - Summer employment, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 157)
    - Computer Print-out Ledgers oversized (Box 13, Folder 158)
      - President's office, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 159)
      - Weekly payroll, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 160)
    - Fair Labor Standard Act: reports, 1970-1976 (Box 15, Folder 161 - 162)
    - Furniture and equipment, 1968-1971 (Box 15, Folder 164)
    - Furniture and equipment, 1971-1975 (Box 15, Folder 165)
    - Graduate Club, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 167)
    - Great Bear Spring Company, 1971-1976 (Box 15, Folder 168)
    - IBM Grant, report on, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 169)
    - Invoices and orders, 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 170)
    - Payroll distribution register, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 172 - 174)
    - Petty cash, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 175)
    - Requests for checks, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 176)
    - Stock requests, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 177)
    - Stock requisitions, 1969-1976 (Box 16, Folder 178)
    - Student employment, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 179)
    - Subscriptions, 1970-1975 (Box 16, Folder 180)
    - Travel form requests, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 181)
    - Travel requisitions, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 182)
    - Xerox, 1969-1975 (Box 16, Folder 183)
- Records concerning community relations, 1939-1977; Accession 1978-A-006
  - Advisees, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advisees, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Albertus Magnus, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Aldermanic Agenda
    - Art Gallery, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - DKE (232 York St.), 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Liquor, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - ZETA PSI, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aldermen, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni
    - New Haven, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Professional and Graduate (Connecticut), undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Undergraduate, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Cyanamid (H. Russell), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arts Council of New Haven, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Association of Yale Alumni
    - AYA Assembly VI, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - AYA Assembly VII, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - AYA Assembly VIII, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Athletic Programs, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 17 - 19)
  - Belgian Visitors, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Benhaven, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bicentennial, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bilingual Program, 1973, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bowl
    - General, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 25 - 26)
    - Bicentennial at the Bowl, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Concerts, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Summer use, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Giants, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Giants - Jets game, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Giants - United Way game, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Jets - Patriots, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Building, grounds and parking, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Campaign for Yale, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Campus Police, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Chamber of Commerce Education Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 37 - 38)
  - Chamber of Commerce Education Committee, issues and action task force, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Citizens Park Council, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - "City Spirit", 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Classrooms, lecture halls, chapels, auditoriums: request for the use and other correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 43 - 45)
  - Colleges, Whitney
    - 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Publicity for, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Commencement, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Community activities (clippings\), 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 51 - 53)
  - Community Affairs, office of development, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Community Progress, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Community Service Programs, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - COSERV - National Council for Community Services t o International Visitors, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Davis, Maggie: Creative Writing Workshop, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Economic Impact Study - Boston Eight, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Economic and Industrial Survey, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Economic Profile and Industrial Directory
    - 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Employee residence distribution, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Energy lecture series, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Esfuerzo Unido, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Extension education, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Financial: Requests for checks
    - 1974 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 69 - 71)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 72 - 73)
  - Gale Research Center, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Gavcez Letter, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Hockey, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Housing, summer, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Hunger Worldwide, Committee on, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 86 - 89)
  - Inter-office memos, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 90 - 91)
  - "Job Analysis of Teaching" ETS Study, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Johns Hopkins, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Junior Science and Humanities Symposium, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Junior Science and Handbook for the "Operation JSHS", 1968 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Juvenile Court, undated (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Juvenile delinquency problem, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Koopers Co., Inc., 1976 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Lead paint, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Lecture series, 1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Libraries, Yale, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Maiz, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Mayhew, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1974- 1976 (Box 10, Folder 105 - 109)
  - Miscellaneous printed material, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 110 - 112)
  - National Alliance of Businessmen, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People and Carp (Center for Advocacy of Research and Planning), 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - National Urban Fellows, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - New England Regional Conference on Career Guidance Institutes, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - New Haven, general, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 117 - 118)
  - New Haven Colony Historical Society, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - New Haven facts, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - New Haven Fire Department, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - New Haven High Schools, 1971-1976 (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - New Haven history, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - New Haven Honorary Degree List, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - New Haven Police Department, 1970-1976 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - New Haven Public Library - Historical Society, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - New Haven Public Schools, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - New Haven Symphony Orchestra, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - New Haven zoning ordinance, 1966, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Nuts and cranks, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - Olin Corporation, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Opportunities Industrialization Center (OIC), 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - P.R.I.S.O.N. (a project to return inmates to schools, occupations and neighborhoods), 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Proofs, reproduction, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Puerto Rican youth services, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - Recycling at Yale, 1974, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Recycling symposium, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - Registrar of Voters, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 138)
  - Sakowitz, Inc. "American Inventions" Bicentennial, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - School of Organization and Management, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Security Committee (University), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 142 - 146)
  - Seven Springs, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 147)
  - Speakers Bureau, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 148 - 150)
  - Telephone, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 151)
  - T.V. Program - Philosophy Project, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 152)
  - T.V. Series - "Story of Italy", 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Tennis Program (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Time-Life Books, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 155 - 156)
  - Town-Gown, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - TRI-RYC, Inc. Training and Research Institute, 1973, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Tri-State Regional Planning Agency, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Undergraduate Admissions Annual Report, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - University regulations, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 161)
  - Upper Chapel Neighborhood (Corp.), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 162)
  - Upward Bound, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 163 - 165)
  - Vaill, George D., retirement, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 166)
  - Volunteer services, 1970-1976 (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Weekend colleges, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Whitney, Eli, Armory site archaeological excavation, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Woolsey Hall, alterations requests, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Woolsey Hall, new piano, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Yale Broadcasting Co. (WYBC), 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Yale Business Forum, undated (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Yale-New Haven Computer Projects, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Yale-New Haven History Education Project, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 176)
  - Yale-New Haven Hospital, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 177)
  - Yale-New Haven Intern Program, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 178)
  - Yale related activities (clippings), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 179 - 185)
  - Yale related activities (clippings), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 186 - 187)
  - Y.M.C.A. - Yale, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 188)
  - Y.M.C.A., 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 189 - 192)
  - Y.W.C.A., 1976 (Box 17, Folder 193)
  - Yale Student Tutoring Agency, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 194)
- Records concerning community relations, 1969-1979; Accession 1979-A-014
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2014
  - Advisees, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Airport [see: Tweed New Haven Airport]
  - Campaign for Yale, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce
    - 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Colleges, Proposed Technical, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Community relations
    - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1977 Jan-Mar (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1977 Apr-Jun (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Community Affairs Development Office, 1974-1976, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Contributions - financial, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Forman Committee
      - 1976-1977 May (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - 1977 Jun-Dec, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Reports from Janet Barnes and David Warren, 1977 November 12 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Galpin Committee
      - "Community Survey... including comparison of white and negro opinions," prepared by Trendex, bound report, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - "General Electric Ten City Study," findings reported by City, summary of findings for all cities, bound volumes, 1976 April 19 - May 16 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - 1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Logue meetings with the Corporation
      - 1976 Sep-Dec (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - 1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Medical School, Cedar Street, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Medical School, Toxicology, 1976, 1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Corporation [Meeting], 1978 March 3 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Economic Development
    - American Airlines, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Bingham and Boyd, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Blunt, Sinnott and Associates, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Blunt, Sinnott and Associates, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - General Foods, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Yale as developer, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Friendship Force, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Golf Course Steering Committee
    - 1972 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 1973 Jan-Feb (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 1973 Mar-1974, no date (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Golf Course reports
    - Notes and drafts, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Notes, drafts and correspondence, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - "Report to the Committee on the Future of the Yale University Golf Course," 3 copies, 1973 March 30 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Heritage Hall Development Corp.
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Cummings Engine Co.: correspondence and initial report, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Drug Wholesaling strategy
      - 1972 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Bound report, 1972 August (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, 1974 February-May (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Annual Report for 1973, 1974 May (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1974 June-November (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Operating plan working papers for 1975, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Project history from E. P. Davison, 1975 October 20 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, I975 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, 1977 February-June (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence, 1977 July-August (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - "A Proposal... for the Creation of and Investment in Heritage Medical Co.," 3 copies, ALS Ralph Hylton to Charles E. Lord, 1977 Sep, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence, 1977 September-October (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence, 1977 November-December (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Outline of History of Yale's dealings with Heritage Hall, includes supporting documents, 1977 December 5 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence, 1978 January-June (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence, 1978 July-December (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Final report, 1978 August 10 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Bound correspondence, memoranda, including Mitchell Report, [1978] (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Exhibits in support of Mitchell Report, includes correspondence, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence, 1979, undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Hispanic Union for Political Action, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - I.B.M. - Handicapped Project, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1969, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - 1977 Jan-May (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - 1977 Jun-Dec (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - "Urban Roadway System 1977, South Central Connecticut," by Regional Planning Agency, bound report, 1977 January (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Randolph, A. Philip institute, undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Regionalism-WELI, Peter Bray, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - South Central Community College, 1973-1977 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Stevens, J.P. Co., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Summer 1978, Dance Festival, Fair Haven (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Tweed New Haven Airport, includes Yale University travel report, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Yale-New Haven Teachers Institute, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Yale-New Haven Teacher's Institute, general, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Yale related activities clippings file, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 86-88)